# **BLAIR REPLOGLE**

#### **Profile**

I've been working in mobile software development for almost a decade. I have a lot of experience working in large, complicated code bases. I prefer tabs. I think code style should aid in readability but not hinder development. I can maintain a codebase or build one from the ground up using best practices. I pride myself in the ability to translate technical problems to non-technical people.

#### **Education**

# **University of Denver**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Double Minor: Mathematics and History

## **Experience**

## Senior iOS Engineer • [2012 - Present]

Wunderman Thompson Mobile — Denver, CO

- Expert knowledge of Swift and Objective-C
- Collaborate with UX, design and developers to build amazing experiences
- Experience working with RESTful API type web services
- Lead development on large scale projects such as the March Madness App

## iOS Software Developer • [2011]

Self Employed — Aspen, CO

- Implemented custom iPhone apps based on client specifications
- Collaborated with designers to implement custom UI elements

#### Mac Genius • [2006-2009]

Apple Inc. — Denver, CO

- Became certified in Apple Hardware and Software
- Managed resources of a dozen repair technicians

### Technical Consultant • [2003 - 2006]

University of Denver — Denver, CO

- Provided technical support to faculty, staff, and students
- Maintained code for University software to configure new student machines

#### **Skills**

- Expert knowledge of Swift and Objective-C
- Experience with PHP and Ruby
- Experience with agile/scrum tools
- Excellent interpersonal, organizational and time management skills
- Experience using Pages for macOS writing this resume